<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cloudburst</string>

    <!-- Navigation Headers -->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="restaurant_header">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="cafe_header">Cafés</string>
    <string name="park_header">Parks</string>
    <string name="mycelium_printer_header">Printers</string>
    <string name="temple_header">Temples</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Names -->
    <string name="restaurant_name_1">Mycelia Feast – Hall of First Harvests</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name_2">Neon Nectar (Established 2135)</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name_3">Solaris Table – Floating Pavilion</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name_4">Fungal Bloom and Sky Gardens</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name_5">The Shimmering Spoon – Central Canal</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name_6">Aurora Harvest, Upper Terrace Dining</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Addresses -->
    <string name="restaurant_address_1">Canal 1, Cloudburst Central</string>
    <string name="restaurant_address_2">Neon Wharf, Cloudburst East</string>
    <string name="restaurant_address_3">Solar Plaza, Level 3</string>
    <string name="restaurant_address_4">Mushroom Walk, Green Sector</string>
    <string name="restaurant_address_5">Shimmer Lane, Cloudburst Heights</string>
    <string name="restaurant_address_6">Aurora Avenue, Central Canal District</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Descriptions -->
    <string name="restaurant_description_1">
        Step into Mycelia Feast, the Hall of First Harvests, where the walls glow with living mycelium and the air hums with faint neon energy. Recommended for its seasonal spore-based delicacies and panoramic canal views, it’s the perfect blend of innovation and serenity in Cloudburst.
    </string>

    <string name="restaurant_description_2">
        Neon Nectar dazzles with vibrant dishes served beneath cascading neon lights that shimmer over the canals. Visitors praise its fusion of bioluminescent flavors and immersive ambiance, making every meal a sensory experience.
    </string>

    <string name="restaurant_description_3">
        Solaris Table offers elevated dining on floating platforms above the central canal. Its solar-infused recipes highlight locally grown ingredients, making it a must-visit for eco-conscious food enthusiasts seeking a taste of Cloudburst’s innovation.
    </string>

    <string name="restaurant_description_4">
        Fungal Bloom and Sky Gardens combines a lush mycelium-covered terrace with open-air seating. Guests love the tranquil atmosphere and creative dishes crafted from the city’s signature spore-based ingredients, perfect for a relaxed afternoon.
    </string>

    <string name="restaurant_description_5">
        The Shimmering Spoon invites diners to experience culinary artistry along the central canal. With its sparkling water reflections and elegant spore-inspired menu, it’s ideal for a romantic evening or special celebration.
    </string>

    <string name="restaurant_description_6">
        Aurora Harvest offers a panoramic view from the upper terrace, showcasing Cloudburst’s flowing canals and glowing cloud formations. Recommended for its fresh seasonal fare and immersive solar-punk ambiance, it’s a feast for both eyes and taste buds.
    </string>


    <!-- Cafe Names -->
    <string name="cafe_name_1">Lumina Brew – Pod 12</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_2">Spore and Steam, East Canal</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_3">Neon Drip (Founded 2142)</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_4">Solar Sip – The Morning Terrace</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_5">The Fungal Cup of Whispering Leaves</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_6">Aurora Bean the Floating Walkway</string>

    <!-- Cafe Addresses -->
    <string name="cafe_address_1">Canal Edge, Cloudburst Central</string>
    <string name="cafe_address_2">Mycelium Walk, Green Sector</string>
    <string name="cafe_address_3">Neon Pier, East Cloudburst</string>
    <string name="cafe_address_4">Solar Promenade, Level 2</string>
    <string name="cafe_address_5">Spore Lane, Cloudburst Heights</string>
    <string name="cafe_address_6">Aurora Arcade, Central Canal District</string>

    <!-- Cafe Descriptions -->
    <string name="cafe_description_1">
        Lumina Brew – Pod 12 offers a cozy retreat along the central canal, with glowing mycelium pods and aromatic brews. Recommended for its unique spore-infused drinks and relaxed floating ambiance.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_description_2">
        Spore and Steam, East Canal, combines artisanal coffee with the subtle hum of neon water reflections. Visitors love its serene atmosphere and the delicate flavors inspired by Cloudburst’s floating gardens.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_description_3">
        Neon Drip (Founded 2142) dazzles with vibrant colors and bioluminescent decor. Recommended for anyone seeking visually stunning drinks paired with creative pastries along the canal walkways.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_description_4">
        Solar Sip – The Morning Terrace sits above the gently flowing canals, bathing patrons in soft solar-inspired light. Its specialty sun-roasted blends and panoramic views make it ideal for a morning ritual.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_description_5">
        The Fungal Cup of Whispering Leaves offers a quiet nook amidst lush mycelium-covered walls. Visitors praise its innovative herbal infusions and the calming, immersive experience it provides.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_description_6">
        Aurora Bean the Floating Walkway features elegant neon-lit seating suspended over the water. Recommended for its experimental beverages and a peaceful view of Cloudburst’s shimmering canal network.
    </string>


    <!-- Park Names -->
    <string name="park_name_1">Luminescent Grove of the First Spore</string>
    <string name="park_name_2">Mycelium Gardens (Founded 2147)</string>
    <string name="park_name_3">Neon Canopy Walk</string>
    <string name="park_name_4">Solar Arcadia - The Floating Terraces</string>
    <string name="park_name_5">Fungal Glade of Whispering Streams</string>
    <string name="park_name_6">Aurora Terrace and Reflection Pools</string>

    <!-- Park Addresses -->
    <string name="park_address_1">Central Canal Park, Level 1</string>
    <string name="park_address_2">Green Sector Promenade</string>
    <string name="park_address_3">Neon Bridge Walk, East Cloudburst</string>
    <string name="park_address_4">Terrace Ring, Solar Plaza Gardens</string>
    <string name="park_address_5">Fungal Walk, Cloudburst Heights</string>
    <string name="park_address_6">Aurora Canal Terrace, Upper Levels</string>

    <!-- Park Descriptions -->
    <string name="park_description_1">
        Luminescent Grove of the First Spore is a magical park where glowing mycelium arches create natural tunnels. Recommended for evening strolls and observing Cloudburst’s shimmering microclimate.
    </string>

    <string name="park_description_2">
        Mycelium Gardens (Founded 2147) showcases carefully cultivated spore flora and floating terraces. Visitors love the harmony of technology and nature, perfect for quiet reflection.
    </string>

    <string name="park_description_3">
        Neon Canopy Walk features towering mycelium trees lit with soft neon highlights. Recommended for scenic walks and photography of Cloudburst’s unique waterway network.
    </string>

    <string name="park_description_4">
        Solar Arcadia – The Floating Terraces offers interconnected sky platforms over canals, where plants and fungi bloom. Visitors praise the combination of panoramic views and eco-friendly design.
    </string>

    <string name="park_description_5">
        Fungal Glade of Whispering Streams is a serene retreat where tiny water channels weave through glowing spores. Perfect for meditation, picnics, or a quiet afternoon immersed in nature.
    </string>

    <string name="park_description_6">
        Aurora Terrace and Reflection Pools captures shimmering cloud reflections in carefully arranged pools. Recommended for sunset strolls and witnessing Cloudburst’s artificial microclimate at its best.
    </string>


    <!-- Temple Names -->
    <string name="temple_name_1">Sunspire Sanctuary</string>
    <string name="temple_name_2">Helios Haven of the Dawn Council</string>
    <string name="temple_name_3">Radiant Dome (Constructed 2132)</string>
    <string name="temple_name_4">Solstice Shrine of Eternal Light</string>
    <string name="temple_name_5">Aurora Altar - Temple of Falling Clouds</string>
    <string name="temple_name_6">Celestial Sun Bath, Upper Zenith</string>

    <!-- Temple Addresses -->
    <string name="temple_address_1">Solar Plaza, Central Cloudburst</string>
    <string name="temple_address_2">Helios Walk, Green Sector</string>
    <string name="temple_address_3">Radiant Terrace, Level 2</string>
    <string name="temple_address_4">Solstice Lane, East Cloudburst</string>
    <string name="temple_address_5">Aurora Avenue, Central Canal District</string>
    <string name="temple_address_6">Celestial Spire, Cloudburst Heights</string>

    <!-- Temple Descriptions -->
    <string name="temple_description_1">
        Sunspire Sanctuary honors the city’s sun deity with towering mycelium spires. Recommended for its breathtaking architecture and tranquil meditation spaces.
    </string>

    <string name="temple_description_2">
        Helios Haven of the Dawn Council offers ritual spaces bathed in solar-infused light. Visitors praise the combination of ceremonial grandeur and serene reflection areas.
    </string>

    <string name="temple_description_3">
        Radiant Dome (Constructed 2132) features a bioluminescent ceiling that mimics sunrise. Recommended for architectural beauty and spiritual immersion in Cloudburst’s unique culture.
    </string>

    <string name="temple_description_4">
        Solstice Shrine of Eternal Light sits atop a floating terrace, connecting nature and ritual. Visitors love its harmonious design and panoramic city views during ceremonies.
    </string>

    <string name="temple_description_5">
        Aurora Altar – Temple of Falling Clouds incorporates cascading water and glowing spores. Recommended for spiritual seekers and photographers capturing Cloudburst’s ethereal ambiance.
    </string>

    <string name="temple_description_6">
        Celestial Sun Temple, Upper Zenith, crowns the tallest canal tower with solar-harvesting panels. Visitors appreciate its blend of technology, spirituality, and breathtaking vistas.
    </string>


    <!-- Mycelium Printer Names -->
    <string name="printer_name_1">Spore Forge Alpha</string>
    <string name="printer_name_2">Mycelium Works - Node 7</string>
    <string name="printer_name_3">BioFab Hub (Experimental)</string>
    <string name="printer_name_4">Fungal Foundry of the Old Colony</string>
    <string name="printer_name_5">Aurora Fabricators – Sky Loop</string>
    <string name="printer_name_6">Neon Grow Labs, Level 5</string>

    <!-- Mycelium Printer Addresses -->
    <string name="printer_address_1">Canal Edge, Green Sector</string>
    <string name="printer_address_2">Central Lab Walk, Cloudburst Central</string>
    <string name="printer_address_3">Bio Plaza, Level 3</string>
    <string name="printer_address_4">Foundry Lane, East Cloudburst</string>
    <string name="printer_address_5">Aurora Arcade, Central Canal District</string>
    <string name="printer_address_6">Neon Wharf, Cloudburst Heights</string>

    <!-- Mycelium Printer Descriptions -->
    <string name="printer_description_1">
        Spore Forge Alpha allows residents to craft mycelium-based furnishings and tools. Recommended for innovative DIY projects and exploring Cloudburst’s sustainable materials.
    </string>

    <string name="printer_description_2">
        Mycelium Works - Node 7 is a bustling hub for community fabrication. Visitors enjoy experimenting with eco-friendly designs and seeing their creations come to life.
    </string>

    <string name="printer_description_3">
        BioFab Hub (Experimental) specializes in experimental mycelium materials and cutting-edge fabrication. Recommended for curious creators seeking unique projects.
    </string>

    <string name="printer_description_4">
        Fungal Foundry of the Old Colony blends traditional craft with modern tech. Visitors love the historical ambiance and hands-on fabrication experiences.
    </string>

    <string name="printer_description_5">
        Aurora Fabricators – Sky Loop features floating platforms for creating lightweight mycelium structures. Recommended for those looking for a visually stunning and functional crafting space.
    </string>

    <string name="printer_description_6">
        Neon Grow Labs, Level 5, is a high-tech fabrication hub with glowing mycelium walls. Visitors praise its futuristic aesthetic and the ability to quickly prototype sustainable designs.
    </string>


    <string name="home_city_description">Cloudburst is a living organism, its bones grown from mycelium. It feeds from a controlled microclimate, generating an ecological delirium. Iconic streaks of cloud weave above radiant canals, where neon capsules skim the waters, tracing paths through mycelium quarters.

    From within this glow you can hear the neon streams flow. And with it, the quiet hum of AI nodes - whizzing orbs that reimagine the world with alien codes.

    Cloudburst is where technology, ecology, and beauty are forever interwoven — a solar sanctuary designed to grow, breathe, and shimmer like a being newly awoken. </string>

</resources>